triplepundit.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy | TriplePundit

### Privacy Policy

3p’s privacy policy is straightforward. You don’t need to identify yourself or your affiliation to access the information on our website. It is our policy is to safeguard the personal information and protect the identity and confidentiality of all visitors and users.

If you choose to subscribe to our [free email newsletter](http://www.triplepundit.com/newsletter/), you need only submit your e-mail address and basic contact information; no additional personal information is required. We promise never to sell, rent, or swap your address with others.  We may occasionally survey you to ask your opinion of how we’re doing — but no more than twice a year.  On rare occasions we’ll send special announcements concerning special TriplePundit projects, in particular, about our CSR training courses.

By registering to comment on the site you also register for our [free email newsletter](http://www.triplepundit.com/newsletter/), however you may opt-out at any time and will not be re-subscribed.

 **Banner advertising:**

As you browse 3p and CSRreporting.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in.  Our display advertising partner, [AdRoll](https://app.adroll.com/), then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with us. The techniques our partners employ **do not** collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.  You can visit this [page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

For more information, [please contact us](mailto:contact@triplepundit.com).
